Guide to the Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archives: Miscellaneous Periodicals Collection ALBA.282
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Milicia Popular (Madrid: Diario del 5th Regimento de Milicias Populares) [See also NYU Library catalogue], Aug 1936 (Box 7)
  - Year I, Number 10, 6 Aug 1936 (Box 7)
- Mirbal (Iberia: La Junta Infantil D'Organitzacio), Undated (Box 5)
  - [Unidentified Issue], Undated (Box 5)
- Modern Monthly (New York) [See also NYU Library catalogue], Sep 1937 (Box 7)
  - Volume X, Number 8 (x2), Sep 1937 (Box 7)
- Mundo Grafico (Madrid), Nov 1937 (Box 5)
  - Year XXVII, Number 1.357, 3 Nov 1937 (Box 5)
  - Year XXVII, Number 1.358, 10 Nov 1937 (Box 5)
- Neighborhood Youth (Brooklyn), Mar 1947 (Box 7)
  - Volume I, Number 2, Mar 1947 (Box 7)
- The New International (New York) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Nov 1934 - Jul 1938 (Box 5)
  - Volume IV, Number 1 (Whole Number 16), Jan 1938 (Box 5)
  - Volume IV, Number 7, Jul 1938 (Box 5)
- New Masses (New York) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Sep 1934- Oct 1939 (Box 5)
  - Volume XII, Number 12 -- "Behind the Headlines in the Textile Strike", 18 Sep 1934 (Box 5)
  - Volume XXX, Number 7 -- "Franco's Ally Defeatism", 7 Feb 1939 (Box 5)
  - Volume XXX, Number 8 -- "Lincoln Brigade Number" (X4 -- 2nd -- pp. 1-2 / 4-5 / 7-14 / 16-17), 14 Feb 1939 (Box 5)
  - Volume XXX, Number 13 -- "What's Happening in Spain", 21 Mar 1939 (Box 5)
- The New Statesman and Nation (London) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], 1939 (Box 5)
  - Volume XVII, Number 421, 18 Mar 1939 (Box 5)
- New York Journal and American (New York), 1 Feb 1939 (Box 2)
  - Number 18,678 ("Roosevelt Faces Revolt on Secret Aid to 'Allies'"), 1 Feb 1939 (Box 2)
- News of Spain (New York: Spanish Information Bureau) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Feb 1938 - Feb 1939 (Box 10)
  - "Franco's Bombings Denounced" (x2), 19 Feb 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Who Lost at Teruel?", 5 Mar 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Dr. Negrin's Report to Parliament" (Cortes Supplement), 5 Mar 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Aragón Offensive", 19 Mar 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Rebel Aviation", 26 Mar 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Aragon and Catalonia", 6 Apr 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Eastern Offensive", 13 Apr 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Stalled Offensive", 27 Apr 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Loyalist Offensives", 1 Jun 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Military Objectives", 8 Jun 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Castellon Sector", 15 Jun 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Non-Intervention Ghost", 22 Jun 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Loyalists Hold Firm", 29 Jun 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Levante Sector", 6 Jul 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Teruel-Sagunto Sector" (x2), 13 Jul 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Third Year of War", 20 Jul 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Surprise Offensive", 27 Jul 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Ebro and Teruel" (x2), 3 Aug 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Another Offensive" (x2), 10 Aug 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Loyalists Hold Gains" (x2), 17 Aug 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Gandesa Sector", 24 Aug 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Loyalist Objectives", 31 Aug 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Ebro Front Holds", Sep 7, 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Loyalist Offensive", 12 Oct 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Rebel Aviation", 26 Oct 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Deadlock", 2 Nov 1938 (Box 10)
  - "New Offensives", 9 Nov 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Two Rivers", 16 Nov 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Ebro Résumé", 23 Nov 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Serge Division", 30 Nov 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Bombing Note", 14 Dec 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Rebel Disaffection", 21 Dec 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Catalonia -- Estremadura" Volume I, Number 2 (x2), 12 Jan 1939 (Box 10)
  - "Italian Intervention" Volume II, Number 3 (x2), 19 Jan 1939 (Box 10)
  - "Fascists in Barcelona" Volume II, Number 4, 26 Jan 1939 (Box 10)
  - "Spain Fights On" Volume II, Number 5, 2 Feb 1939 (Box 10)
  - "The Central Zone" Volume II, Number 6, 9 Feb 1939 (Box 10)
  - "Madrid: Capital of Spain" Volume II, Number 7, 16 Feb 1939 (Box 10)
- No Veas (Madrid: Semenario Humoristico), 1937 (Box 10)
  - Year 1, Number 16, 4 Sep 1937 (Box 10)
- La Noche (Barcelona: CNT-AIT), 1937 (Box 5)
  - Year XIV, Number 3,565, 16 Apr 1937 (Box 5)
  - Year XIV, Number 3,577, 30 Apr 1937 (Box 5)
- Noi Donne: Nous les Femmes (Paris), 1937 (Box 10)
  - Year II, Number 8 [?], Nov 1937 (Box 10)
- Nosotros (Valencia), Sep 1937 (Box 5)
  - Year II, Number 151, 2nd Series, 16 Sep 1937 (Box 5)
  - Year II, Number 153, 2nd Series, 18 Sep 1937 (Box 5)
- Las Noticias (Barcelona: Organo del Comite de Cataluna de la UGT), 31 Jul 1937 - 25 Jan 1939 (Box 4)
  - Year XLII, Number 14.124, 31 Jul 1937 (Box 4)
  - Year XLIII, Number 14.482, 22 Sep 1938 (Box 4)
  - Year XLIV, Number 14.588, 25 Jan 1939 (Box 4)
- El Noticiero Universal (Barcelona), Apr 1938 (Box 10)
  - Year LI, Number 16.953, 4 Apr 1938 (Box 10)
- Nova Iberia (Barcelona: Comissariat de Propaganda de la Generalitat de Catalunya) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Feb - Apr 1937 (Box 4)
  - Number 2, Feb 1937 (Box 4)
- Nuestro Ejercito (Barcelona: Sociedad General de Publicaciones), 1938 (Box 10)
  - Year I, Number 2/3, May/Jun 1938 (Box 10)
- L'Organisation de la Defense du Patrimoine Artistique et Historique Espagnol Pendant La Guerre Civile (Paris: Office International des Musees) [See also NYU Library catalogue], 1937 (Box 10)
  - Volume 39/40 (x2), 1937 (Box 10)
- Our Fight: Nuestro Combate (Barcelona and Madrid: 15eme International Brigade ) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Sep 1937 - Oct 1938 (Box 4)
  - Number 35 (x3), Dec 1937 - Jan 1938 (Box 4)
- Our Sunday Visitor (Huntington, IN), Nov 1938 - Jan 1939 (Box 4)
  - Volume XXVII, Number 29, 20 Nov 1938 (Box 4)
  - Volume XXVII, Number 37, 15 Jan 1939 (Box 4)
- El Parapeto (Valencia: CNT/AIT, Organo del Comite Nacional), 14 Aug 1937 (Box 4)
  - Year I, Number 17, 14 Aug 1937 (Box 4)
- Photo-History (Concord, NH: Modern Age Books) [See also NYU Catalogue], Apr 1937 (Box 4)
  - Volume I, Number I (x5), Apr 1937 (Box 4)
- Pionero Rojo (Barcelona: Semanario de los Ninos Obveros y Campesinos), May 1937 (Box 10)
  - Year I, Number [?], 27 May 1937 (Box 10)
- Poder y Libertad (Madrid: Federacion Clubs Vindicacion Feminista), 1989 (Box 10)
  - Number 11 - "50 Years de Lucha (1939-1989), Homenaje a las Mujeres de la Guerra Civil Espanola", 2nd Semestre 1989 (Box 10)
- Prometeo (Brussels), 10 Nov 1935 (Box 2)
  - Year VIII, Number 124, 10 Nov 1935 (Box 2)
- Protestant Digest (New York) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Mar 1940 (Box 10)
  - Volume III, Number 3, Mar 1940 (Box 10)
- La Rambla (Barcelona: Portantveu del Partit Socialista Unificat de Catalunya), 30 Aug 1937 (Box 2)
  - Year VIII, Number 820, 30 Aug 1937 (Box 2)
- Reconquista, Undated (Box 10)
  - Supplemento, 35 Division, Undated (Box 10)
- Refugiados (Washington D.C.: Organo del Comite Central Espanol Pro-Ayuda Refugiados), 20 Jun 1939 (Box 2)
  - Volume I, Number 2, 20 Jun 1939 (Box 2)
- The Register (Denver: International News Service, National Edition) [fragile / consult staff], Nov 1938 - Jan 1939 (Box 2)
  - Volume XIV, Number 46, 13 Nov 1938 (Box 2)
  - Volume XIV, Number 47, 20 Nov 1938 (Box 2)
  - Volume XV, Number 3, 15 Jan 1939 (Box 2)
- La Republique Espagnole Au Service De La Cultura (Cachon, France), Undated (Box 10)
  - [Unidentified Issue], Undated (Box 10)
- Resumen de Informacion de Espana (Mexico: Partido Comunista de Espana), 1943 (Box 10)
  - Number 2, 1943 (Box 10)
- Revista de Revistas (Mexico: Semanario de Excelsior), Jul - Oct 1986 (Box 10)
  - Number 3990, 18 Jul 1986 (Box 10)
  - Number 3991, 25 Jul 1986 (Box 10)
  - Number 3994, 15 Aug 1986 (Box 10)
  - Number 3995, 22 Aug 1986 (Box 10)
  - Number 3996, 29 Aug 1986 (Box 10)
  - Number 3998, 12 Sep 1986 (Box 10)
  - Number 4000, 26 Sep 1986 (Box 10)
  - Number 4001, 3 Oct 1986 (Box 10)
  - Number 4002, 10 Oct 1986 (Box 10)
- Revista de Sanidad de Guerra (Madrid: La Jefatura de Sanidad del Ejercito), Sep 1937 (Box 11)
  - Year I, Number 5, Sep 1937 (Box 11)
- Ruta (Barcelona: FAI-FIJL, Anarquista - Organo de las Juventudes Libertarias de Cataluna), 2 Sep 1937 (Box 3)
  - Year II, Number 46, 2 Sep 1937 (Box 3)
- El S.R.I. y Su Obra - Congreso Popular de la Solidaridad (Madrid: Comite Provincial Madrid), Jul 1937 (Box 11)
  - Jul 1937 (Box 11)
- Semana (Madrid: Falange), 1940 (Box 3)
  - Year I, Number 32, 1 Oct 1940 (Box 3)
  - Year I, Number 33, 8 Oct 1940 (Box 3)
  - Year I, Number 34, 15 Oct 1940 (Box 3)
  - Year I, Number 35, 22 Oct 1940 (Box 3)
- Servicio Espanol de Informacion - textos y documentos (Barcelona), 12 Feb 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 376, 12 Feb 1938 (Box 3)
- Socialist Appeal (Chicago) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], 1936-1937 (Box 9)
  - Volume II, Number 7, Aug 1936 (Box 9)
  - Volume II, Number 8 (x2), Sep 1936 (Box 11)
  - Volume II, Number 9, 1 Oct 1936 (Box 9)
  - Volume II, Number 10, 1 Nov 1936 (Box 11)
  - Volume III, Number 1 (x2), Jan 1937 (Box 11)
  - Volume III, Number 2, Feb 1937 (Box 11)
- El Socialista (Madrid: Organo del Partido Socialista Obrero), 1934, 1936, & 1937 (Box 3)
  - Year XLIX, Number 8.008, 4 Oct 1934 (Box 3)
  - Year LI, Number 8175, 30 Jun 1936 (Box 3)
  - Year LII, Number 8578 (x2), 23 Sep 1937 (Box 3)
- El Soldado de la Republica (Madrid: Journal de la XIVeme Brigada), Oct 1937 (Box 11)
  - Number 50 (x3), 8 Oct 1937 (Box 11)
- Solidaridad Internacional Antifascista (New York: "La Voz"), Feb 1939 (Box 11)
  - CARTA - CIRCULAR Number 23, Feb 1939 (Box 11)
- Solidaridad Obrera (Barcelona: CNT-AIT, Comite Regional de Catalunya ) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], 1937 & 1943 (Box 2)
  - Year VIII, Number 1588, Epoca VI, 14 May 1937 (Box 2)
  - Year IX, Number 2099, Epoca IV, 18 Jan 1939 (Box 2)
- Solidaridad Obrera (Mexico: Portavoz de la Militancia Cenetista en el exilio), May 1943 (Box 2)
  - Year II, Number 26, 15 May 1943 (Box 2)
  - Year II, Number 27, 29 May 1943 (Box 2)
- Soviet Russia Today (New York: F.S.U. Publications) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], 1937 & 1941 (Box 11)
  - Volume 5, Number 12, Feb 1937 (Box 11)
  - "Special Section II", Volume VI, Number 12 (x2), Feb 1937 (Box 11)
  - Volume 10, Number 6, Oct 1941 (Box 11)
- Die Soziale Revolution: Frontzeitung (Barcelona: (CNT-FAI) Herausgegeben Von Den Deutschen Anarchosyndikalisten), 1 May 1937 (Box 2)
  - Number 12, Sondernummer, 1 May 1937 (Box 2)
- Spain (New York: United Youth Committee to Aid Spanish Democracy) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Undated (Box 11)
  - "The Spanish War in Pictures" (x2), Undated (Box 11)
- Spain Today (Madrid: Communist Party of Spain) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], 1937 & 1953 (Box 3)
  - "Unity - the key to victory" from the political bureau of the Communist Party of Spain, Sep 1937 (Box 3)
  - Number 4, Oct 1937 (Box 3)
  - "The Fall of Asturias: Two Important Statements" (x2), Nov 1937 (Box 3)
  - Volume VI, Number 6 (London: International Brigade Association and Friends of Republican Spain), Jan 1953 (Box 3)
- Spain Today (New York: Committee for a Democratic Spain) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Jan 1962 - Sep 1969 (Box 3)
  - Volume I, Number 5, Jan 1962 (Box 3)
  - Volume I, Number 6, Feb - Mar 1962 (Box 3)
  - Volume I, Number 7, Apr - May 1962 (Box 3)
  - Volume I, Number 8, Jun 1962 (Box 3)
  - Volume II, Number 1, Sep - Oct 1962 (Box 3)
  - Volume II, Number 3, Jan - Feb 1963 (Box 3)
  - Volume II, Number 4, Mar - Apr 1963 (Box 3)
  - Volume II, Number 5, May - Jun 1963 (Box 3)
  - Volume III, Number 3, Dec - Jan 1964 (Box 3)
  - Volume IV, Number 1, Sep - Oct 1964 (Box 3)
  - Volume IV, Number 2, Nov - Dec 1964 (Box 3)
  - Volume IV, Number 4, May - Jun 1965 (Box 3)
  - Volume IV, Number 5, Oct - Nov 1965 (Box 3)
  - Volume VI, Number 1, Nov 1967 (Box 3)
  - Volume VII, Number 5, Sep 1969 (Box 3)
- Spanish Information Service: Texts and Documents (Barcelona: Spanish Service Information), Dec 1937 - Apr 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 1 (x2), 10 Dec 1937 (Box 3)
  - Number 2 (x2), 17 Dec 1937 (Box 3)
  - Number 3, 24 Dec 1937 (Box 3)
  - Number 4, 31 Dec 1937 (Box 3)
  - Number 5, 7 Jan 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 7, 21 Jan 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 8, 28 Jan 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 8 [Misprint: 9?], 4 Feb 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 10, 11 Feb 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 11, 18 Feb 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 12, 25 Feb 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 13 (x2), 4 Mar 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 14 (x2), 11 Mar 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 15, 18 Mar 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 16 (x2), 25 Mar 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 17 (x3), 1 Apr 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 18, 8 Apr 1938 (Box 3)
  - Number 19, 15 Apr 1938 (Box 3)
- Spanish Refugee Relief Campaign (New York) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Feb 1940 (Box 11)
  - Bulletin: "American Rescue Ships For Spain's Refugees", Feb 1940 (Box 11)
- The Spanish Revolution (Barcelona: POUM) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Dec 1936 - May 1937 (Box 11)
  - Volume I, Number 9, 23 Dec 1936 (Box 11)
  - Volume II, Number 7, 21 Apr 1937 (Box 11)
- Tampa Bay History (San Antonio, FL: University of South Florida), 1997 (Box 11)
  - Volume 19, Number 2, Fall / Winter 1997 (Box 11)
- Temas Espanoles (Madrid: Publicaciones Espanolas), 1953, 1956, & 1959 (Box 11)
  - Number 54 "Las Checas", 1953 (Box 11)
  - 2nd Series, Number 39 (pp. 1-30) "Onesimo Redondo", 1956 (Box 11)
  - 2nd Series, Number 73 "El Santuario de Santa Maria de la Cabeza", 1956 (Box 11)
  - 2nd Series, Number 163 "Prisioneros del Teruel", 1959 (Box 11)
- Tiempos Nuevos (Barcelona: Tierra y Libertad) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], 1936 - 1937 (Box 12)
  - Year IV, Number 7/8 (x2), Jul/Aug 1937 (Box 12)
- Tiempos Nuevos (Toulouse: Revista del Movimiento Libertario Español), May 1946 (Box 12)
  - Year II, Number 10, May 1946 (Box 12)
- Time (New York) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], 24 Sep 1936 (Box 3)
  - Rehearsal "Dummy" Number 2, 24 Sep 1936 (Box 3)
- Trincheras (Barcelona: Las Juventudes Socialistas Unificadas), Undated (Box 3)
  - Number 1, Undated (Box 3)
  - Number 2, Undated (Box 3)
- Triunfo (Madrid and Barcelona), 17 Apr 1971 (Box 3)
  - Year XXVI, Number 463 ("1931 Tres Dias de Abril"), 17 Apr 1971 (Box 3)
- Umbral (Valencia: CNT and UGT), 1937 - 1938 (Box 12)
  - Number 1, 10 Jul 1937 (Box 12)
  - Number 49, 22 Oct 1938 (Box 12)
- L'Undomptable (Valencia: CNT-FAI-AIT), Oct 1937 (Box 12)
  - Year 1 - Hebdomadaire - Number 39, 7 Oct 1937 (Box 12)
- L'Universel (Anvers, Belgium: Falange), Undated (Box 2)
  - Year 4, Number 3 - (Espagne), Undated (Box 2)
- Vanguard (New York: Vanguard Group) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Dec 1936 - Nov 1938 (Box 12)
  - Volume 3, Number 5, Dec 1936 (Box 12)
  - Volume 3, Number 8, Aug 1937 (Box 12)
  - Volume 4, Number 1, Nov 1937 (Box 12)
  - Volume 4, Number 2 (x2), Feb 1938 (Box 12)
  - Volume 4, Number 3, Apr 1938 (Box 12)
  - Volume 4, Number 4, Jul 1938 (Box 12)
  - Volume 4, Number 5/6, Nov 1938 (Box 12)
- Vanguardia (Valencia: Diario del Comisariado del Ejercito de Levante), 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - Year II, Number 210, 18 Jul 1937 (Box 2)
  - Year II, Number 63, 8 Feb 1938 (Box 2)
- La Vanguardia de Los Ninos, Dec 1937 - Jan 1938 (Box 12)
  - Number 1, 30 Dec 1937 (Box 12)
  - Number 2, 6 Jan 1938 (Box 12)
  - Number 3, 13 Jan 1938 (Box 12)
  - Number 4, 20 Jan 1938 (Box 12)
  - Number 5, 27 Jan 1938 (Box 12)
- Vertice (Bilbao: Revista Nacional de la Falange Espanola Tradicionalista y de las J.O.N.S.), Nov 1937- Jul 1938 (Box 2)
  - Year II, Number 6, Nov 1937 (Box 2)
  - Year II, Number 10, May 1938 (Box 2)
  - Year II, Number 12, Jul 1938 (Box 2)
- Vida Obrera (Albacete: Organo de la Unificacion Marxista), 9 Sep 1937 (Box 2)
  - Year I, Number 32, 9 Sep 1937 (Box 2)
- Le Volontaire De La Liberte (Madrid: Organe des Brigades Internationales), Oct 1937 (Box 12)
  - Deutsche Ausgabe No. 49. (x5), 6 Oct 1937 (Box 12)
  - Edizione italiana. No. 45, 14 Oct 1937 (Box 12)
- The Volunteer (New York: Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], Sep - Oct 1938 (Box 2)
  - Multiple issues, 1957-1972 (Box 16)
  - Multiple issues, 1973-2011 (Box 17)
- The Volunteer for Liberty (London: International Brigade Association) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], 1942-1943 (Box 12)
  - Volume 3, Number 5 (x2 - Second copy missing pp. 1-2 & 23-24), [Jul?] 1942 (Box 12)
  - Volume 4, Number 2 (x5), [Apr?] 1943 (Box 12)
  - Volume 4, Number 4 (x2), Jun 1943 (Box 12)
  - Volume 4, Number 5 (Box 12)
  - Volume 4, Number 6 (x2), Sep 1943 (Box 12)
  - "For Polish Freedom" (x6), Nov-Dec 1943 (Box 12)
- The Volunteer for Liberty (Madrid and Barcelona: XVth International Brigade) [See also NYU Library Catalogue], 1937 (Box 13)
  - Multiple issues, Jul 1937-Dec 1937 (Box 13)
  - Multiple issues, 1938 (Box 14)
- The Volunteer for Liberty (New York: Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade) [See also New York University Library Catalogue]
  - Multiple issues, 1938-1953 (Box 15)
  - Multiple issues, 1954-1957 (Box 16)
- Voz de Madrid (Madrid: Semanario de Informacion y Orientacion de la Ayuda a la Democracia Espanola), 10 Sep 1938 (Box 2)
  - Year I, Number 9, 10 Sep 1938 (Box 2)
- La Voz Leninista (Barcelona: Organo de la Seccion Bolchevique Leninista de Espana), Aug 1937 (Box 3)
  - Year I, Number 1, Apr 1937 (Box 3)
  - Year I, Number 2, 23 Aug 1937 (Box 3)
- La Voz de la Sanidad de la XV Divison (Madrid), 1937 (Box 12)
  - Number 11, 7 Sep 1937 (Box 12)
- VU (France), 29 Jul 1936 (Box 2)
  - Year 9, Number 437 "Nos photographes en Espagne Guerre Civile Visions d'Horreur", 29 Jul 1936 (Box 2)
- War Bulletin (Boston: Communist Party of Massachusetts), 7 Oct 1939 (Box 2)
  - Volume I, Number 3, 7 Oct 1939 (Box 2)
- Westcoast Volunteer (Los Angeles: Henry Easton Post, Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade), 1941 (Box 12)
  - Volume 1, Number. 5, Jun & Jul 1941 (Box 12)
- World News and Views (London: H.R.G. Jefferson) [See also NYU Library Catalogue] (Box 12)
  - Volume 19, Number 7, Feb 18, 1939 (Box 12)
  - Volume 19, Number 10, Mar 11, 1939 (Box 12)
  - Volume 19, Number 11, Mar 15, 1939 (Box 12)